Okay. Hello. Welcome to this uh video. I
know this is a bit of an odd one like
all my content, but today we are doing
an unboxing video.
How do you do these things? So, in the
mail yesterday, uh I received a very
exciting package. About a month ago, I
was given the opportunity to do a little
bit of a collab with War Cry. I think
that's how you say it. Wry War Cry. and
they basically let me try out some of
their stuff and it arrived today. So,
I'm really excited to see
uh what's
see my design that's come to life
basically. I'm I'm very excited. There's
a few things in this one. There's a few
different things. First of all, have the
first package. I have no clue what
what's in this one. I think it might be
stickers.
Oh, it is stickers.
Look at that.
Oh, that's so cute.
Oh, they're adorable.
Look at that. It's not focusing. Focus.
Don't focus on me. Do I have to do the
influencer thing where I have to like
Hold it up so it focuses.
Look how cute that is though. Oh my
days. Oh, and then there's the donut
ones.
I got like
So, the good thing about the uh war cry
is you can do like so many custom
options. So, like this one here, you
can't see very well, but it's like
if I tilt it around,
it's like it's glittery.
And it looks awesome. Oh my days, that
looks so cool.
All right. And then the last one.
Last one is the screaming exalle. It
doesn't really show up on camera, but it
I think it's supposed to kind of have
like a little hollow
effect. Yeah. You can you can kind of
see it in the camera there.
I love it so much. Oh my days. Okay, so
that's the stickers.
We got so much more than that, though.
All right, second package.
What's this one? Forgot what it was. I
actually for kind of forgot what I
ordered.
Yes. Oh my days. Oh my days. This is one
I was really excited for. Hold on.
Look.
Oh my gosh.
What's the word?
Ah. Ah. Ah. Ah. That looks so good. Oh
my days. I love that. Oh, I'm looking
forward to unboxing that one in a sec.
All right. Hold on.
Oh, I need to assemble it myself.
Okay. Okay. So, look at this, guys.
Hang on. Oh, let me let me let me
simulate this and then I'll
A few moments later.
Look at that.
Oh my.
Look how cute that is. I don't think
I've done this right, but like
look if you I don't know if you can cuz
it's not going to focus unless I do the
influencer thing. It's you can't really
see it, but it's it's it's glittery and
it's beautiful. Got my own custom cocoa
kit keychain, guys. Oh my days. Let me
know if you guys want one because I
might look into that. You never know.
This might be my new favorite thing
ever.
It's a little robot.
That is the cutest thing I've ever seen.
I'm Hold on.
Look at it go
or not. Look how adorable it is. And the
last [music] thing that I ordered, this
was just a bit of fun because like,
you know, when you get the opportunity
to do these, you do it. You know,
I thought, you know,
I don't really like my current mouse
pad. Why not get a mouse pad with my art
on it?
It's so beautiful. No, no, cuz actually
it's like cuz this is one of the more
high quality artworks I've done, right?
But it's actually such high quality and
it's beautiful and I love it so much.
Same with like everything else. Like
it's such high quality. It's such like
absolute perfection. I'm in love with
everything here. The other thing I've
forgot to mention about W cry is there's
lots of custom options you can like as
you can see this is one of the little
bits they gave me for the keychain right
there's so much more you can do I think
it was a heart one you can do bows you
can do any pretty much any shape any
color you can as you can see I don't
know if you can see with the little
robot it's like a kind of a rainbow one
you can do that but with keychains it's
just super easy website to get around
great prices amazing quality
So many options. It's actually like
hurts my head how many options there
are. And like they even give you spare
bits as well. Like I only got one
keychain, but they gave me like
five little key. There it goes. Five
keychain bits. So I will definitely be
using
war cry in the future. I really enjoyed
uh
doing [music] this little collab. Thank
you for allowing me to try out your
products. I am doing a little giveaway
of stickers over on my Instagram if you
want to go check that out and maybe earn
yourself win yourself some little
[music] little freebies, some little
goodies. So, the link is in the bio.
So, yay. All right. Well, thank you for
watching this silly little influencer
video. There may be a few of those to
come in the future. Who knows? Thanks
for watching, guys. See [music] you
later.